Salvador Luria Papers 1923-1992 Mss.Ms.Coll.39
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1938-1992; 15.5 linear feet
  - Boston University, 1965-1980 (Box 7)
  - Boston West Biology Round Table, 1983-1984 (Box 7)
  - Botan, E.A., 1960 (Box 8)
  - Botstein, David, 1972-1983 (Box 8)
  - Boulware, Kathleen Gaines, 1973 (Box 8)
  - Bourgeois-Cohn, Suzanne, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Bowles, Jean A., 1957 (Box 8)
  - Bowman, Bernard U., Jr., 1963 (Box 8)
  - Brachet, Jean Louis Auguste, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Bradford Books, Publishers, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Bradshaw, Ralph A., 1989 (Box 8)
  - Brandeis University, 1960-1979 (Box 8)
  - Brandly, C.A., 1956 (Box 8)
  - Branley, Franklyn M., 1957 (Box 8)
  - Braun, Armin, 1962 (Box 8)
  - Bravo, Ernesto, 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Bray, Dennis, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Brenner, Sydney, 1960-1961; 4.0 Item(s) (Box 8)
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Lectures, public speaking; Massachusettes Institute of Technology
  - Brewer, Gregory J., 1974-1985 (Box 8)
  - Brey, Robert Newton III, 1978-1986 (Box 8)
  - Brink, R.A., 1962 (Box 8)
  - Brinton, Charles C., Jr., 1961, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Bristol-Myers Company, 1985 (Box 8)
  - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1981 (Box 8)
  - Brock, Thomas D., 1984 (Box 8)
  - Bronk, Detlev, 1966 (Box 8)
  - Jacob Bronowski Centre for the Humanities, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Brooke, Edward W., 1973 (Box 8)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory, 1959 (Box 8)
  - Brooks, Frank E., 1963 (Box 8)
  - Brooks, Toby, 1970 (Box 8)
  - Brooks, Werner C., 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Brothers, Marietta, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Brown, John, 1971-1972 (Box 8)
  - Brown University, 1973-1976 (Box 8)
  - Buggs, C.W., 1957 (Box 8)
  - Bukhari, Ahmad I., 1982 (Box 8)
  - Bulger, William M., 1965 (Box 8)
  - Bunka Hoso Development Centre Ltd., 1974-1975 (Box 8)
  - Bunting, Mary I., 1960, 1963 (Box 8)
    See also Ser.I, Dushman, Miriam B.
  - Burdette, Walter J., 1962 (Box 8)
  - Burman, Lars G., 1983 (Box 8)
  - Burrous, Jeanne W., 1959 (Box 8)
  - Burrous, Stanley E., 1958, 1960 (Box 8)
  - Burrows, T.W., 1957 (Box 8)
  - Burton, Kenneth, 1961 (Box 8)
  - Burzatta, Giovanni, 1962 (Box 8)
  - Bush, John, 1974 (Box 8)
    Bush, Sheila
  - Bush, Sheila (Box 8)
    See Ser.I, Bush, John
  - Buzzati-Traverso, Adriano A., 1961-1962 (Box 8)
    -See also Ser.I, International Cell Research Organization
    -See also Ser.I, International Laboratory of Genetics and Biophysics
  - Bylinsky, Gene, 1973 (Box 8)
  - Cahn, Florence H., n.d. (Box 8)
  - Cairns, John, 1960-1990 (Box 8)
    See also Ser.I, International Cell Research
  - Calareso, Josephine, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Calef, Enrico, 1956-1974 (Box 8)
  - Calendar, Richard, 1968 (Box 8)
    Bertani, Giuseppe
  - Califano, L., 1960 (Box 8)
  - Calkins, H.E., 1956 (Box 8)
  - Callaway, W. Ragan, 1971 (Box 8)
  - Calvin, Melvin, 1959-1961 (Box 8)
  - Cambridge Forum, 1979, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Cameron, Kenneth Neill, 1982, 1984, n.d. (Box 8)
  - Cammeron, Dennis, 1959 (Box 8)
  - Campaign for Peace with Justice in Central America, 1982 (Box 8)
  - Campbell, Allen McCulloch, 1957-1965 (Box 8)
  - Campbell, Bill (Box 8)
    See Ser.I, Campbell, Joan
  - Campbell, Joan, 1969 (Box 8)
    Campbell, Bill
  - Campion, Francis X., 1982 (Box 8)
  - Canadian Journal of Microbiology, 1956 (Box 8)
  - Candelas, Graciela C., 1987 (Box 8)
  - Cantoni, G.L., 1963 (Box 8)
  - Cantor, Marvin H., 1980 (Box 8)
  - Cardinali, Giuseppe, 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Carlson, Elof Axel, 1970; 3.0 Item(s) (Box 8)
    American Association for the Advancement of Science; Conferences and symposia; History of biology, especially genetics; Muller, Hermann Joseph; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1957-1981; 10.0 Item(s) (Box 8)
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Carnegie Institution of Washington; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Demerec, Milislav; Lectures, public speaking; Recommendations; Requests for reprints
  - Carregal, Enrique J.A., 1982 (Box 8)
  - Carter, Herbert E., 1957-1959 (Box 8)
  - Casadaban, Malcolm, 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - Case Western Reserve University, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Caspari, Ernst Wilhelm, 1957, 1959; 2.0 Item(s) (Box 8)
    Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Committee activities; Demerec, Milislav; International Congress of Genetics
  - Castelleja, David, 1980-1981, n.d. (Box 8)
  - Cavalli, Luca, 1956, 1960 (Box 8)
  - Cavallito, Chet J., 1956 (Box 8)
  - Cavard, Daniele, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - Center for Science in the Public Interest, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - Centre National de la Recherche Scientifique (Box 9)
    See also Ser.IIb, same title
    - Folder #1, 1939-1940, 1973-1978 (Box 9)
    - Folder #2, 1979-1981 (Box 9)
  - Centre Royaumont (Box 9)
    See Ser.I, Fondation Royaumont
  - Centro de Investigacion y de Estudios Avanzados, 1962 (Box 9)
  - Ceppellini, Ruggero, 1963 (Box 9)
  - Chamberlain, Owen, 1970 (Box 9)
    Townes, Charles H.
  - Chan, Russell K., 1973 (Box 9)
  - Chandrasekhar, S[ubrahmanyan], 1984 (Box 9)
  - Chang, William, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Cheng, Peter, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Chester, Thomas J., 1967 (Box 9)
  - Jane Coffin Childs Memorial Fund, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Chin, Michael, n.d. (Box 9)
  - Cho, Nancy, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Chomskey, Noam, 1985, n.d. (Box 9)
    See also Ser.I, Basso, Lelio
  - Chorover, Stephan, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Chovnick, Arthur, 1959-1984 (Box 9)
  - Christensen, J. Roger, 1963 (Box 9)
  - Christensen, W. Blake, 1958 (Box 9)
  - Chung, Raymond, 1970 (Box 9)
  - Cianciarulo, Nikki, 1986-1988 (Box 9)
  - The Ciba Foundation, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Citizens Committee Concerned with Freedom of the Press, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Citizens Committee for a Nuclear Test Ban Treaty, 1963 (Box 9)
  - Citizens League Against the Sonic Boom, 1968 (Box 9)
  - City of Hope National Medical Center, 1973, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Clark, John, 1961-1962 (Box 9)
  - Clark, Virginia L., 1975-1988 (Box 9)
    See also Ser.I, Davis, Bernard D.
  - Clayton, Roderick K., n.d. (Box 9)
  - Cleveland Clinic Foundation (Box 9)
    - Folder #1, 1982-1987 (Box 9)
    - Folder #2, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Folder #3, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Folder #4, 1987-1988 (Box 10)
  - Cline, John C., 1958 (Box 10)
  - Clowes, Royston C., 1956-1963 (Box 10)
  - Coetzee, J.N., 1961 (Box 10)
  - Coffman, Glenn R., 1961 (Box 10)
  - Cohen, Amikam, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Cohen, Daniel Bernard, 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - Cohen, Denise, 1960 (Box 10)
  - Cohen, Michael David, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Cohen, Peter, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Cohen, Philip P., 1971 (Box 10)
  - Cohen, Seymour S., 1949, 1956-1957; 12.0 Item(s) (Box 10)
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Conferences and symposia; Publication -- Science; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Cohn, Melvin, 1956-1969 (Box 10)
    Lennox, Edwin S.
    -See also Ser.I, The Salk Institute for Biological Studies
  - Colby College, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Cole, Charles Norman, Jr., 1973 (Box 10)
  - Cole, Warren H., 1960 (Box 10)
  - Collaborative Research, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 10)
    See also Ser.III, same title
  - Collège de France, 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - Collins, E.B., 1957 (Box 10)
  - Collins Publishers, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Colorado State College, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Colten, Margery Sue, 1980, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Colten, Milton, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Columbia University, 1940-1990; 37.0 Item(s) (Box 10)
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Columbia University; Committee activities; Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Horwitz Prize; Delbruck, Max; Graduate study; Honors -- Horwitz Prize; Honors -- Sc.D.; Lectures, public speaking; Political issues; Publication; Radiation genetics; Research support; Teaching; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Comité du Centenaire de Lucien Daniel, 1960 (Box 10)
  - Commager, Henry Steele, 1966 (Box 10)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Education in the Biological Sciences, 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - Committee for a Sane Drug Policy, 1972, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Committee for Effective Drug Abuse Legislation, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Committee on Problems of Disarmament, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Committee on the Impact of Biomedical Research, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Commoner, Barry, 1957, 1962, 1970 (Box 10)
    See also Ser.I, International Convocation
  - Cook, Ann, 1960-1961 (Box 10)
  - The Coop, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Cooper, Peter D., 1960 (Box 10)
  - The Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Cope, Arthur C., 1964 (Box 10)
  - Cormack, Allan M., 1962 (Box 10)
  - Cornell University, 1955-1968 (Box 10)
  - Corner, Thomas R., 1963 (Box 10)
  - Council for a Livable World, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Courchesne, William E., 1984 (Box 10)
  - Cramer, William A., 1980-1987 (Box 10)
    See also Ser.I, Suit, Joan L.
  - Crawford, Irving, 1963 (Box 10)
  - Crick, Francis H. C., 1959, 1985, n.d.; 3.0 Item(s) (Box 10)
    See also Ser.I, The Salk Institute for
    Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Harvard University; Nobel Committee for Physiology or Medicine; Recommendations
  - Cristwell, Ann Rose, 1956-1957 (Box 10)
  - Crofutt, Lawrence, 1956 (Box 10)
  - Cronan, John, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Cummings, Donald J., 1962, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Curtiss, Roy, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Daedalus, 1967-1976 (Box 10)
  - Dai Dong, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Dalby, Arthur, 1958 (Box 10)
  - Daniels, Donna L., 1982, 1986 (Box 10)
  - D'Arcais, Francesco, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Darling, Paul G., 1974 (Box 11)
  - Darnell, James E., Jr., 1961-1974 (Box 11)
    Becker, Yechiel
  - Darnton, Robert, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Dartmouth College, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Davidson, Norm, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Davis, Bernard D., 1955-1984 (Box 11)
    Clark, Virginia L.
    -See also Ser.I, Harvard Medical School
    -See also Ser.I, McCormick, John W.
  - Dazian Foundation for Medical Research, 1940-1955 (Box 11)
  - Dean, Willard W., [195-] (Box 11)
  - De Benedetti, S., 1982 (Box 11)
  - de Blasio, Mary, 1954 (Box 11)
  - de Groot, B., 1971 (Box 11)
  - De Hevesy, G[eorge], 1938 (Box 11)
  - Dejour, Dominique, 1985 (Box 11)
  - Marcel Dekker, Inc., 1971, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Delachaux et Niestle, 1970, 1972 (Box 11)
  - De la Garza-Curcho, Mercedes, 1971-1981 (Box 11)
  - Delbrück, Manny, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Delbrück, Max, 1943-1972; 9.0 Item(s) (Box 11)
    American Association for the Advancement of Science; Bacterial genetics; Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Conferences and symposia; Lectures, public speaking; Oak Ridge National Laboratory; Publication; Radiation genetics; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Delegation for Basic Biomedical Research, 1981 (Box 11)
  - Delihas, Nicholas, 1960 (Box 11)
  - Del Santo, Linda, 1957 (Box 11)
  - De Luca, H.F., 1959 (Box 11)
  - Demain, Arnold L., 1964 (Box 11)
  - DeMars, Robert Ivan, 1953-1961, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Demerec, M[ilislav], 1949; 1.0 Item(s) (Box 11)
    Conferences and symposia; Oak Ridge National Laboratory
  - DeMoss, Ralph D., 1956-1959 (Box 11)
  - Dershowitz, Ann, 1971 (Box 11)
  - de Santillana, Giorgio, 1966 (Box 11)
  - Desmond, Thomas C., 1960 (Box 11)
  - Dev, S.B., 1984 (Box 11)
  - Devasli, Yair, 1985 (Box 11)
  - de Vicente, Román, 1961 (Box 11)
  - DeVita, Vincent T., Jr., 1982 (Box 11)
  - Devoret, Raymond, 1983 (Box 11)
  - de Vries, Andre, 1961 (Box 11)
  - DeWitt, Susanne K., 1961 (Box 11)
  - Diamandopoulos, George Th., 1974 (Box 11)
  - Dickinson, William C., Jr., 1967-1968 (Box 11)
  - Di Gerolamo, Mario, 1959, 1961 (Box 11)
  - di Mayorca, G.P., 1961 (Box 11)
  - Dispenzieri, Angela, 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Dodson, Jeffrey D., 1973 (Box 11)
  - Djordjevic, Bozidar, 1956 (Box 11)
  - Dobzhansky, Theodosius, 1959-1973; 8.0 Item(s) (Box 11)
    Bacterial genetics; Biographical and personal data; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Columbia University; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Nobel Prize; Crow, James F.; Genetics Society of America; Molecular genetics; Monod, Jacques; Publication; Wallace, Bruce
  - Doermann, August H., 1949, 1956-1962 (Box 11)
  - Dolesh, Carole J., 1958 (Box 11)
  - Dollars and Sense, 1974, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Douglas, William O., 1974 (Box 11)
  - Dove, William F., 1963 (Box 11)
  - Drake, John W., 1958-1968 (Box 11)
  - Drexler, Henry, 1981 (Box 11)
  - Dubos, René, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Duc, Nguyen H., 1962 (Box 11)
  - Duckworth, Donna H., 1972 (Box 11)
  - Dulbecco, Renato, 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Dunkell, Samuel V., 1983 (Box 11)
  - Dunn, L. C. (Leslie Clarence), 1956-1962; 7.0 Item(s) (Box 11)
    Biographical and personal data; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Demerec, Milislav; Federation of American Scientists; Lectures, public speaking; Political issues
  - E.I. Du Pont de Nemours and Company, 1954-1957 (Box 11)
  - Durand, René R., 1956, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Durkin, James H., 1975 (Box 11)
  - Dushman, Miriam Bonita, 1961-1964 (Box 11)
    Baker, Thomas I.
    Bunting, Mary I.
    Mandel, Manley
    Markovitz, Alvin
    -See also Ser.I, Baker, Thomas I.
    -See also Ser.I, Christensen, J. Roger
    -See also Ser.I, Demain, Arnold L.
    -See also Ser.I, Markovitz, Alvin
  - Dutchess Community College, 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Dycus, A.M., 1957 (Box 11)
  - Dyson, Freeman, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Ebisuzaki, Kaney, 1965 (Box 11)
  - Eccles, John, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Edel, Abraham, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Edgar, Robert S., 1956-1973 (Box 11)
    -See also Ser.I, Stahl, Franklin W.
    -See
  - Edsall, John T. (Box 11)
    See Ser.I, American Academy of Arts and
  - Edwards, Philip R., 1955-1958 (Box 11)
    Guha, A.
    -See also Ser.I, Guha, A.
  - Efner, Jane Ann, 1955-1956 (Box 11)
  - Egami, Fujio, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Albert Einstein College of Medicine, 1955-1980 (Box 11)
    Horecker, B.L.
    White, Abraham
  - Eisen, Herman, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Eisenstadt, Jerome, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Eisenstein, Elizabeth, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Elghammer, W. Robert, 1956-1957 (Box 11)
  - Elizur, Erela, 1960 (Box 11)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Emmott, Kirsten, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Englesberg, Ellis, 1956-1961 (Box 11)
  - Engley, Frank B., 1956 (Box 11)
  - Ephrati-Elizur, E., 1969 (Box 11)
  - Ephrussi, Boris, 1959; 1.0 Item(s) (Box 11)
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Cancer, chemotherapy; Requests for reprints
  - Epstein, Herman T., 1956 (Box 11)
  - Epstein, Richard H., 1957-1962 (Box 11)
  - Erber, Bruno, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Ercoli, N., 1955-1956 (Box 11)
  - Erickson, G., 1981 (Box 11)
  - Ernster, Lars, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Errera, M. (Box 11)
    See Ser.I, Thomas, R.
  - Esso Education Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 12)
  - Estrich, Susan R., 1988 (Box 12)
  - Etzioni, Amitai, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Eureka College, 1956 (Box 12)
  - European Molecular Biology Organization, 1967-1972 (Box 12)
  - Evans, Nina Ruth, 1956 (Box 12)
  - Evans, Titus C., 1956 (Box 12)
  - Ewing, W.H., 1955-1957 (Box 12)
  - Ezekiel, David, 1957 (Box 12)
  - Faculty for Human Rights in El Salvador and Central America, 1983-1985 (Box 12)
    See also Ser.IIa, Central America
  - Fagen, Richard R., 1983 (Box 12)
  - Fairbanks, Grant, Jr., 1969-1970 (Box 12)
  - Fairleigh Dickinson University, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Faldini, Giorgio, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Falk, Richard A., 1973, 1980 (Box 12)
  - Falkow, Stanley, 1961-1963 (Box 12)
  - Fan, David, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Fan, Mei-Ling Judy, 1984-1987 (Box 12)
  - Fano, Virginia, 1970 (Box 12)
  - FEBS Letters, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Feder, Ned (Box 12)
    See Ser.I, Stewart, Walter W.
  - Federation of American Scientists (Box 12)
    - Folder #1, 1956-1970 (Box 12)
    - Folder #2, 1971-1975, n.d. (Box 12)
  - Feigelson, Philip, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Feigenbaum, Joel, 1970 (Box 12)
  - Feingold, David Stuart, 1973-1980 (Box 12)
  - Feld, Steven L., 1982 (Box 12)
  - The Fellowship of Reconciliation, 1971 (Box 12)
  - Fenner, Frank, 1957-1967 (Box 12)
  - Fermi, Enrico, 1938 (Box 12)
  - Fernstrom, John D. (Box 12)
  - Ferrero, Ernesto, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Feshbach, Herman, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Fetner, Robert H., 1956 (Box 12)
  - Field, Alexander J., 1969 (Box 12)
  - Fields, Kay Louise, 1973-1990 (Box 12)
  - Fine, Jacob, 1967 (Box 12)
  - Fischer, Ernst-Peter, 1981 (Box 12)
  - Fischer Fantuzzi, Lia, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Fisher, Agnes C., 1977 (Box 12)
  - Fishman, David, 1971 (Box 12)
  - Fleet, Shelley, 1969-1970 (Box 12)
  - Fogel, Marian, 1969 (Box 12)
  - Folkman, Judah, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Fondation Royaumont (Box 12)
    - Folder #1, 1970-1971 (Box 12)
    - Folder #2, 1972 (Box 13)
    - Folder #3, 1973-Sep. 1974 (Box 13)
    - Folder #4, 1974-1978 (Box 13)
  - Fondazione Alfredo Apolito, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Fondazione Giovanni Lorenzini, 1970 (Box 13)
  - Food and Disarmament International, 1983-1984 (Box 13)
  - Foor, Forrest, 1974 (Box 13)
  - The Ford Hall Forum, 1970 (Box 13)
  - Fornili, Sandro, 1971 (Box 13)
  - Fortune, 1960-1961 (Box 13)
  - Foster, John W., 1959 (Box 13)
  - Fot, Maury, 1965 (Box 13)
  - Foulds, John, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Fox, C. Fred, 1972 (Box 13)
  - Fox, Maurice Sanford, 1960-1980 (Box 13)
  - Fraenkel, Dan, 1976 (Box 13)
  - Francis, Thomas, Jr., 1962, 1964 (Box 13)
  - Franklin, Richard M., 1958 (Box 13)
  - Franklyn, Naomi, n.d. (Box 13)
    See also Ser.I, Mandel, Manley
  - Fraser, Dean, 1949, 1956-1958 (Box 13)
  - Fraser, Dorothy, 1967 (Box 13)
  - Fredericq, P., 1961, 1963 (Box 13)
  - Freeman, Harold, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Frei, Emil III, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Fremlin, J.H., 1971 (Box 13)
  - Friedman, Milton, 1976-1977 (Box 13)
  - Frumin, Steven, 1968 (Box 13)
  - Fry, Cynthia, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Fuchs, Ephraim Joseph, 1980 (Box 13)
  - Fuchs, Ralph F., 1956 (Box 13)
  - Fudenberg, H. Hugh, 1974, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Fuhrman, Shella, 1970 (Box 13)
  - Fukumi, Hideo, 1957 (Box 13)
  - Fukasawa, Toshio, 1965, 1970 (Box 13)
  - Fulton, Chandler, 1963 (Box 13)
  - Funk, Forest J., 1960 (Box 13)
  - Furness, G., 1961 (Box 13)
  - Gajdusek, D[aniel] Carleton, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Gaffron, Hans, 1969 (Box 13)
  - Garen, Alan, 1951-1971 (Box 13)
  - Garen, Sue, 1961 (Box 13)
  - Garmise, Louis, 1961 (Box 13)
  - Gavin, James M., 1968 (Box 13)
  - Gefter, Malcolm Lawrence, 1971 (Box 13)
  - Gelman, George, 1961-1962 (Box 13)
  - Genetics, 1956-1957 (Box 13)
  - Genetics Society of America, 1963, 1969, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Gentry, Sharron, 1971 (Box 13)
  - Georgopoulos, Constantine Panos, 1975-1978 (Box 13)
  - Gersh, Eileen S., 1971 (Box 13)
  - Gerstein, Lee, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Gifford, George E., 1958 (Box 14)
  - Gilbert, Walter, 1967 (Box 14)
  - Gilmour, Marion, 1956-1957 (Box 14)
  - Ginsburg, Victor, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Gitler, C., 1973 (Box 14)
  - Gittleson, Celia, 1970 (Box 14)
  - Glass, H. Bentley, 1959; 1.0 Item(s) (Box 14)
    Carnegie Institution of Washington; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory
  - Glenn, John, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Gloger, Barry, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Gobbo, Gino, 1971-1974 (Box 14)
  - Godchamp, Walter III, 1963 (Box 14)
  - Goldberg, Edward, 1969, 1976 (Box 14)
  - Goldfarb, David, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Goldhaber, Samuel Z., 1970 (Box 14)
  - Goldie, James H., 1985 (Box 14)
  - Goldman, Martin, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
  - Goldschmidt, Eugene P., 1962 (Box 14)
  - Goldstein, Geraldine, 1968-1969 (Box 14)
  - Goldstein, Walter, 1966 (Box 14)
  - Goldwasser, Edwin L., 1986 (Box 14)
  - Goldwasser, Robert Abraham, 1961 (Box 14)
  - Gordan, Irving, 1963 (Box 14)
  - Gordan Research Conference, 1949-1983 (Box 14)
  - Gore, Albert, Jr., 1981 (Box 14)
  - Gorini, Annamaria Torriani, 1971 (Box 14)
  - Gorini, Luigi, 1967, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Gorrill, R.H., 1959 (Box 14)
  - Gould, Stephen J., 1979, 1984 (Box 14)
    See also Ser.I, The Benjamin/Cummings
  - Grace, Carolyn Carr, 1971 (Box 14)
  - Graduates of Italian Medical Schools, 1970 (Box 14)
  - Granoff, Allan, 1959 (Box 14)
  - Greeley, William Roger, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Green, D. MacDonald, 1959 (Box 14)
  - Green, Melvin, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Greenglass, Donna L., 1963 (Box 14)
  - Greenspan, Harvey P., 1974 (Box 14)
  - Grell, Rhoda F., [196-] (Box 14)
  - Grey, Ron M., 1962 (Box 14)
  - Grib, Norman, 1968 (Box 14)
  - Groman, Neal, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Gros, François, 1969 (Box 14)
    See also Ser.I, International Cell
  - Gross, Paul R., 1973, 1981 (Box 14)
  - Grossman, Jerome, 1967, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Grunert, Dick, 1957 (Box 14)
  - Guarente, Leonard, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Guerrini, Franco, 1968 (Box 14)
  - Guillemin, Roger, 1974 (Box 14)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1952-1965 (Box 14)
  - Guha, A., 1957 (Box 14)
    Edwards, Philip R.
    -See also Ser.I, Edwards, Philip R.
  - Gunsalus, Irwin C., 1956-1979 (Box 14)
    See also Ser.I, Stanier, Roger
  - Gupta, B.M., 1962 (Box 14)
  - Gustafson, Wendell N., 1976 (Box 14)
  - Gustavus Adolphus College, 1985-1986 (Box 14)
    See also Ser.III, The Single Artificer
  - Guterman, Sonia K., 1971-1982 (Box 14)
  - Guttman, Burton S., 1961, 1971 (Box 14)
  - Haber, Howard, 1981, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Habing, Ruth, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
  - Haff, Dick, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Hagemann, G., 1963 (Box 14)
  - Hagen, David, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Hall, Dwight H., 1974-1986 (Box 14)
  - Hall, Nancy Levine, 1969-1970 (Box 14)
  - Halle, Morris, 1978, 1980 (Box 14)
  - Halpern, Yeheskel S., 1970 (Box 14)
  - Halvorson, Harlyn Orin, 1957-1960 (Box 14)
    See also Ser.I, Lewis Rosenstiel Award
  - Hamburger, Viktor, 1987 (Box 14)
  - Hammer, Rose Mary (Box 14)
    See Ser.I, Boicourt, Rose Mary
  - Hamon, Yves, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Hampshire College, 1969-1970 (Box 14)
  - Handler, Philip, 1972 (Box 14)
  - Hannan, Mark W., 1957 (Box 14)
  - Hanson, R.P., 1957 (Box 14)
  - Harm, Walter, 1961, 1963 (Box 15)
  - Harold, Franklin M., 1974 (Box 15)
  - Harper and Row, Publishers, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Harrar, Georgetta (Box 15)
    See Ser.I, Streisinger, George
  - Harris, Fred, 1976 (Box 15)
  - Harris, R.J.C., 1959 (Box 15)
  - Hartman, Philip Emil, 1959-1962 (Box 15)
  - Hartwell, Leland H., 1972 (Box 15)
  - Harvard Medical School, 1956-1990 (Box 15)
  - Harvard University, 1973-1974, 1981 (Box 15)
  - Haselkorn, Robert, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Hashimoto, Kazuo, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Hattman, Stanley M., 1963-1984, n.d. (Box 15)
  - Haurowitz, Felix, 1960 (Box 15)
  - Haverford College, 1957 (Box 15)
  - Hayes, William, 1957-1963 (Box 15)
  - Hebrew University, 1968-1969 (Box 15)
    Keynan, Alexander
  - Hedén, C.-G., 1960, 1962 (Box 15)
  - Hedges, R.W., 1959-1962 (Box 15)
  - Heidelberger, Michael, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Heilbrunn, L.V., 1957 (Box 15)
    See also Ser.I, Protoplasmatologia
  - Heist, Carroll E., 1956 (Box 15)
  - Helling, Robert B., 1965 (Box 15)
  - Hellman, Martin E., 1982 (Box 15)
  - Helsinki, Donald, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Henle, Werner, 1957 (Box 15)
  - Herman, Robert K., 1963 (Box 15)
  - Hershey, Alfred D., 1949, 1955-1963; 27.0 Item(s) (Box 15)
    Bacterial genetics; Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Biographical and personal data; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Demerec, Milislav; Editorial matters; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Molecular genetics; Publication; Radiation genetics; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Hertlein, 1957 (Box 15)
  - Hertzberg, Sidney, 1976 (Box 15)
  - Heston, W.E., 1960 (Box 15)
  - Higa, Akiko, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Hill, George, 1960 (Box 15)
  - Hill, Helene Z., 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Hill, Miroslav, 1987 (Box 15)
  - Hirata, Hajime, 1972 (Box 15)
  - Hirsch, Martin, 1970, n.d. (Box 15)
  - Ho, John, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Hoaglund, Mahlon B., 1976 (Box 15)
  - Hobbs, John B., 1963 (Box 15)
  - Hobby, Gladys L., 1967 (Box 15)
  - Hoffmann-Berling, H., 1960 (Box 15)
  - Hofschneider, P.H., 1962 (Box 15)
  - Hogness, Dave, 1952 (Box 15)
  - Holden-Day, Inc., 1962 (Box 15)
  - Hollaender, Alexander (Box 15)
    See Ser.I, Oak Ridge National Laboratory
  - Holland, I.B., 1973 (Box 15)
  - Hollister, Leo, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Holloway, Bruce W., 1960, 1967 (Box 15)
  - Homburger, Freddy, 1963 (Box 15)